Register of the Delafield (Wis.). Clerk: Clerk's Records, 1890-1968
Wisconsin Historical Society
Delafield (Wis.). Clerk: Clerk's Records, 1890-1968
Delafield (Wis.). Clerk
Waukesha Series 21
0.4 c.f. (1 archives box)
Housed at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries Archives Department / Milwaukee Area Research Center; owned by the Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
A variety of records primarily from the early 1960s concerning public welfare, city finances, zoning, the municipal court, and other matters.
Contents List
- Audit Report, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Board of Zoning Appeals, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Common Council Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Financial Records, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Highway and Zoning Matters, 1890-1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Municipal Court, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Nagawicka Lake Heights Assessment, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Post Office, no date (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Public Welfare
  - 1959-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Quit Claim Deeds, 1929-1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Report of the Clerk to the Department of State Audit, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Schedule of Accounts for Cities, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Water Safety Patrol, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)